（春野はるのサクラ）ハア ハア…
（サクラ）ハア ハア…
（チヨ）サクラ！ うっ…
Sakura!
チヨバア様 大丈夫ですか？
まだ動けますか？
Grandmother Chiyo!
Are you okay?
Can you still move?
（サソリ）
ほう この傷で他人の心配か
Oh? You're worrying about other people
even with this wound?
（サクラ）うっ！ ううっ…
（チヨ）サソリ どうして…
Sasori... How...?
まさか…
Don't tell me...
そうじゃったのか…
So that's it.
If you're a Medical Ninja,
（サソリ）医療忍者なら 自分が
どういう状態か分かってるはずだが
you should understand
the situation you're in.
（サクラ）うるさい
Shut up!
フッ　気丈な娘だ
だが いつまで もつかな？
You're a courageous girl.
But how long can you hold on?
ううっ！ ハア ハア ハア…
（サソリ）こいつ 刀が
突き刺さったままで止血と治癒を…
She's... stopping the bleeding
and healing herself with
a sword stuck in her.
器用なヤツだ
She's skilled.
チヨバア様…　私は大丈夫です
Grandmother Chiyo, I'm okay.
だから 早く解毒薬を…
So hurry up and
take the antidote.
サクラ…
Sakura.
ううっ！ ハア ハア ハア…
フフフッ　毒が効いてきたようだな
It looks like the poison
is starting to take effect.
もちろん この刀も毒刀だからな
Of course, this sword
is also poisoned, you see.
（サクラ）毒で体がしびれて
チャクラがうまくコントロールできない
My body's getting numb
from the poison,
so I can't control
my Chakra very well.
ハア ハア ハア…
ハア ハア…
♪～
A voice heard in the distance gives me a hint.
tooku de kikoeru koe wo hinto ni
One by one like-minded people are standing up.
hitori mata hitori tachiagaru doushi
Lets overturn all the everyday, monotonous things.
kurikaesu dake no fudan doori kutsugaesu
I'm ready, are you ready?
junbi iize are you ready
A shiver spreads through my body, violently ringing stomping.
karadajuu furuwasu shindou ni hageshiku uchinarase yo stomping
Constantly stirring in me, it calls me.
taezu tsuki ugokasu call me
Catching that unchanging, never wavering story, Come on!
kawarazu yuru ga nutsukamu story come on
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
Are you ready for a few risks?
hey yo whoa tashou no risuku wa kakugo desho
You have to get up no matter how many times you fall. (Get it on!)
nanka korundatte tatsu get it on
It's not some conspiracy, just a paper-thin session
nare ai ja nai ze kami hitoe no sesshon
The pent up feelings turn into a crystal.
irikunda kanjou kidzukiageta kesshou
The rising cheers will become your courage.
wakiagaru kansei ga yuuki tonaru
So stand up now, no matter how much pain you feel.
tachiagareba ima ijou kurushimi tomonau
But in the end I'm sure you'll laugh.
soredemo saigo wa kitto warau
Everything will be swept away in victory and cheer.
subete sarau shouri to kansei
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
～♪
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
（チヨ）
ハア ハア…
Impossible Dream
ん…
（サソリ）そいつか 解毒薬は…
So that's the antidote.
どうして？
Why?
チヨ… バア様？
Grandmother... Chiyo...
（サソリ）
どいつもこいつも他人のために
死を選ぶとは… くだらねえ
I can't believe how everyone chooses
death for the sake of others...
How stupid...
（サクラ）ぐっ…
うっ… くうっ
（サソリ）んっ　あっ…
（サクラ）うっ…
はなさない
I won't let go.
（サソリ）うくっ…
この小娘 なんて力だ
This girl's got... incredible strength.
（チヨ）ハア ハア…
Grandmother Chiyo!
チヨバア様！
（サソリ）こいつと
力比べしてもムダか
It's futile to have
a strength contest with her, huh?
だったら…
Then...
ああっ！
Die!
死ねえ！
ハア ハア…
（サソリ）な… なんだと
Wh-What?
（チヨ）ハア ハア…
（サソリ）あっ…
最後に気を抜いたの サソリ…
You lowered your guard
at the end, Sasori.
（サソリ）何？
What?
ああっ
（チヨ）これで お前は動けぬ
Now you can't move.
当たりじゃろ
Am I right?
いくら カラクリの体とはいえ…
Although you may have
the body of a puppet,
チャクラを扱うお前には
どうしても 生身の部分がいる
you use Chakra, so you need
a part that's living...
それが弱点じゃ
That's your weakness.
そして…
And just that part from
your left chest
あの抜け殻から左胸の その部分だけは
そっくり そのまま抜けている
is missing from that shell.
ここだ！
Here!
（サソリ）ああっ…
（チヨ）恐らくは
術が完成する直前に
It was probably right before
the Jutsu was completed.
ほかのカラクリに 乗り換えた…
You switched...
to a different puppet.
カラクリの体は
つまりは ただの人形
The body of a puppet
is basically just a doll.
お前の 本体は…
Your real body...
チャクラを生み出す
その胸のパーツじゃ
is that chest part that
produces Chakra.
ヘッ…
ああ…
Sakura!
サクラ！
こりゃ いかん
This is not good.
（チヨ）とにかく 傷口を塞ぎながら
この刀を抜いてしまわねば
In any event, I've got to
pull out this sword
while closing the wound.
フッ…　うっ
ぐっ！
我慢せい
Hang in there.
うう… うっ！
もう少しじゃ
Just a little more.
ハア…
ムダだ　急所を突いた
It's futile. I pierced
a vital point.
毒がなくとも
そいつは もうじき死ぬ
She'll soon be dead even
without poison.
出血が多すぎる
She's lost too much blood.
あんたも医療忍者だからな
Since you're also
a Medical Ninja,
簡単には治療できないところを狙った
I aimed for a spot
you can't easily heal.
フッ　医療忍術での応急処置は
すでに終えた
I've already finished first-aid treatment
with Medical Ninjutsu.
わしが今やっておるのは
医療忍術ではない
What I'm doing right now
isn't Medical Ninjutsu.
（サソリ）何？
What?
（チヨ）己の生命エネルギーを
そのまま 分け与える…
I'm giving her
my own life energy.
Don't tell me...
（サソリ）まさか…
（チヨ）転生忍術じゃ
It's a Reanimation Ninjutsu!
転生忍術…
A Reanimation Ninjutsu.
そもそも これは
お前のために長年かけ編み出した...
It's a Jutsu I spent years
creating originally for you...
わしだけの術じゃ
one that only I can use.
この術があれば傀儡くぐつにすら
命を吹き込むことができる
With this Jutsu...
life can even be breathed
into puppets.
術者じゅっしゃの命が尽きるのと交換でな
In exchange for the life
of the caster that is...
（チヨ）サソリ…
Sasori.
じゃが…
But in hindsight, it's a dream
that won't be realized...
今となっては もはや
かなわぬ夢だがの
（サソリ）くだらねえ
How stupid...
（幼少サソリ）いってらっしゃい
Have a safe trip.
バ… バカな
It... It can't be...!
おのれ 木こノ葉はの白い牙め
Damn you...
White Fang of the Leaf!
あっ… チヨバア様！
Grandmother Chiyo!
父様と母様が帰ってきたの？
Are Mother and Father back?
ん…
違うの？
They're not?
（チヨ）そ… それが お主の父と母は
W-Well, your mom and dad were
suddenly sent on another mission...
急に別の任務に就くことになっての
帰ってくるのは まだ
しばらく先になりそうなのじゃ
It looks like they won't be back
for a little while.
ええ？
I just heard from them
わしと一緒に帰りを待てと
連絡が入ったところじゃ
and they want you to wait
with me for them to return.
待てるな？ サソリ
Can you wait, Sasori?
うん…
Yeah.
くだらねえな
いつからぼけた？ ババア
How stupid.
When did you grow senile, Grandma?
おっ
サクラ 大丈夫か？
Sakura, are you okay?
Yes.
（サクラ）はい
チヨバア様こそ
What about you, Grandmother Chiyo?
ん？ おかしいな
That's strange.
その転生忍術とやら
I thought the caster of that
Reanimation Ninjutsu or whatever
死んだヤツに命を吹き込む代わりに
術者が死ぬんじゃなかったのか
was supposed to die
in exchange for breathing life
into someone dead.
サクラは致命傷ではあったが
死んでいたわけではない
Sakura's wound was severe,
but she wasn't dead...
So I got off without
serious injury.
だから わしも
この程度で済んだのじゃ
（サソリ）そりゃあ 残念だ
That's unfortunate.
ハア ハア ハア…
I'd stop that.
やめておけ
この体は痛みすら感じない
This body doesn't
even feel pain.
（サクラ）ハア ハア…
The more you hit me,
the greater the pain in your fist.
（サソリ）殴るだけ
お前の拳が痛むだけだ
女ってのはムダなことをするのが
好きなヤツらだな
Women sure like to
do stuff that's pointless.
フフフ…
俺は その血のつながった
そのババアが死のうが
I won't feel anything
even if my blood-related grandmother
should die.
何も感じはしない
心も この体と同じだ
My heart is just like
this body.
Up until now I've killed hundreds,
thousands of people.
今まで 何百何千と殺してきたが
そのうちの１人と同じだ
She'd be the same
as one of them.
もっと 物事は単純だ
Things are simpler that way.
（サクラ）あんた…
人の命をなんだと思ってんだ！
Just what do you think
a person's life is to you?!
肉親をなんだと思ってんだ！
What do you think
a relative is to you?!
Come on... Is that what
a Shinobi should be saying?
おい…
それが忍びの言うセリフか？
あっ…
なんで… あんたは なんで
そんな考え方しかできないんだ
Why?
Why can you only think
like that...?
（チヨ）サクラ…
Sakura...
もういい
That's enough.
でも…
But...!
こヤツを
こんなふうにしてしまったのは…
It was the evil customs
and teachings of Hidden Sand Village.
わしら 砂隠すながくれの
あしき風習と教えじゃ
that made him what he is.
チヨバア様…
Grandmother Chiyo.
お前も この体になってみるか？
Do you want to have
a body like this?
そうすれば 俺の言ってることも
少しは分かるだろうぜ
If you did,
you'd probably somewhat understand
what I'm talking about.
くっ…
朽ちぬ体だ
寿命に縛られることもない
This body won't decay and
it's not bound to a span of life.
傀儡人形なら
いくらでも造り直せる
A puppet can be recreated
over and over again.
人など傀儡で
いくらでも造り出せばいい
I can create as many people
as I want with puppets.
欲しけりゃ だが…
If you want, that is...
It's not just about increasing
the amount.
数を増やせばいいってもんじゃない
コレクションは質だからな
A collection is all about quality.
（サクラ）あんたは 一体なんなんだ
What the hell are you?!
I'd venture to say
あえて言うなら
人形になりきれなかった人間 …か
I'm a human who couldn't
completely become... a puppet.
I'm a puppet,
俺は傀儡だが生身の核を持つ
不完全な傀儡だ
but an incomplete puppet
possessing a living core.
人でもなく 人形でもない
I'm not a person...
nor am I a puppet.
もうじき動かなくなる
I'll soon stop moving.
その前に俺も
ムダなことを１つしてやろう
Before that, I think
I'll do something pointless...
俺を倒した褒美だ
It's your reward for defeating me.
んっ？
（サソリ）お前は大蛇丸おろちまるのことを
知りたがっていたな
You wanted to know
about Orochimaru, right?
あっ…
草隠くさがくれの里さとにある
天地橋てんちきょうに10日後の真昼に行け
At midday in ten days,
go to the Tenchi Bridge located
in the Village Hidden in the Grass!
どういうこと？
What do you mean?
I've got a spy working...
大蛇丸の部下に
俺のスパイがいる
as one of Orochimaru's
subordinates...
そこで そいつと落ち合う…
ことに… なって…
I was supposed to rendezvous...
with him... there...
終わりました　チヨバア様
It's over, Grandmother Chiyo.
さすがです
Excellent work.
いや… 本来なら倒されていたのは
わしのほうじゃった
No. I was the one who should've...
been defeated.
え？
What?
サソリには
わしの最後の攻撃が見えとった
Sasori read my final attack.
じゃが どういうわけか
かわせなかった
But for some reason,
he didn't dodge it.
少しの隙が生じた
A slight opening was revealed.
Could it be that he...?
それって もしや…
（うずまきナルト）
カカシ先生 まだかよ
Kakashi-sensei,
aren't you ready yet?
（はたけカカシ）そろそろ ＯＫだ
It's about ready now.
（ナルト）それが さっき言ってた…
That's the thing
you were talking about before?
（カカシ）そうだ 新しい写輪眼しゃりんがんだ
That's right.
It's my new Sharingan.
（カカシ）行くぞ ナルト
（ナルト）おう！
Let's go, Naruto!
Right!
♪～
Just like always.
daitai itsumo doori ni
As I turn that corner.
sono kado wo magareba
I am lost in the waves of people.
hitonami ni magire komi
Melting, disappearing.
tokete kiete iku
I lose my way.
boku wa michi wo nakushi
I even completely lose my words.
kotoba suranaku shite shimau
But just one thing.
dakedo hitotsu dake wa
Remained, remained.
nokotteta nokotteta
Your voice.
kimi no koe ga
Your smiling faces, your angry faces, everything.
warau kao mo okaru kao mo subete
Keeps me walking on.
boku wo arukaseru
Surely, when I see the point where the clouds have broken.
kumo ga kireta saki wo mitara kitto nee
You know what I mean?
wakaru desho
nee wakaru desho
～♪
Next Episode
戦うほどに 相手が 強くなるなんて
The more we fight,
the stronger they get!
こうなったら 僕たちも
裏モードをオンにするしかありませんね
It looks like
we have no choice,
but turn on our Reverse Mode!
裏モード？
Reverse Mode?
解説しよう　俺たち ガイ班は
究極ピンチのときに限り
Allow me to explain!
We, Team Guy, only under
an ultimately critical situation,
１度だけ 心身に蓄積してきた...
can fully activate for
a single time,
the Powerful Youth Burning Young Power
stored within our mind and body,
強烈な 熱血青春ヤングパワーを
フル稼働させることにより
増幅された 集中力と気合いで
using it to increase
our concentration and kiai,
一瞬だけ 爆発的な破壊力を
手に入れることができるのだ
and for a flash of a second,
attain an explosively destructive power!
よ～し 今こそ行くぞ リー！
All right!
Lee, now is our time to do this!
はい！ ガイ先生！
Yes! Guy-sensei!
ちょっと待ちなさい！
Now just hold on for
a second!
そんな設定は 一切ない！
There is no such thing!
Beasts: Alive Again
次回「蘇よみがえる獣けものたち」
Next time: "Beasts: Alive Again"
（ナルト･リー）
恋のライバル
— Rivals of love.
（リー）いやあ 最近の
サクラさんの活躍 すごすぎますよ
Man, Sakura-san has been
kicking a lot of butt lately!
（ナルト）ああ！ なんか
ムチャクチャ いい感じだよな
Yeah! She's like really awesome!
（リー）強く 賢く 美しい
She's strong! She's smart!
And she's beautiful!
あの日 あのとき
I fell in love at first sight
出会った瞬間 一目ぼれした 僕の目に
間違いはなかった
the moment I met her
back on that day.
My eyes were not mistaken!
（ナルト）は～ん 思いっきり
ドン引きされてたくせによ
Heh. But she totally tried to
get away from you.
大体さ
There's no way she'd give
someone like you, Bushy Brow,
サクラちゃんがゲジ眉なんか
相手にするわけねえってばよ
the time of day to begin with.
（リー）あのときは…
（ナルト）ん？
We just didn't know each other
very well back then!
お互いに
よく知らなかっただけです
And besides, I don't want to hear that
from someone who tried to
それに サスケ君に化けて
サクラさんに近づこうとした君に
get close to her
by transforming into Sasuke-kun.
そんなこと
言われたくありませんね
Wha--? That happened ages ago!
バカ…
む… 昔の話だろうが！
ふん！ 俺ってば 今度こそ
Humph! Next time for sure
I'll get her to notice me with my skill.
実力で サクラちゃんを
振り向かせてみせるもんね
Well, we're on the same team, after all.
まあ 同じ班だし
誰かさんよかはチャンスあるしな
I've actually got a chance
unlike a certain someone.
くうっ！ でも忘れないでください
But don't forget who you
had your memorable first kiss with!
君の記念すべき
ファーストキスの相手は…
ダ～ ダメ ダメ ダメ！
No-no-no!
Don't look!
見ちゃ
ダメだってばよ～